(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon, Aunties Kitchen)
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong, Wandering Panda)
(Hong Seok Cheon and Jung Ho Young, Chef Land)
(Kim Ho Yoon and Kim Kwan Hoon, Crazy Flavor Restaurant)
(Kim Hoon and Choi Sang Hyun, Kids Restaurant)
(Lee Sung Hoon and Go Seok Hyun, Lulu Land)
(Among six alliance teams,)
(only 2 teams to sell 100 servings survive.)
It's over.
(Wandering Panda, Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
(1st place in the 1st half)
(All teams have now entered the second half.)
(Where did everyone flock to at the start of the second half?)
(Ordering)
(Kids Restaurant that put their dessert front and center)
(The 1st survival on Round 3)
(Kids Restaurant, Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon)
(Currently, Wandering Panda is...)
(in last place.)
(Wandering Panda is on the verge of elimination.)
(Now there's only one spot left.)
(Which team will be the final survivor of Round 3?)
- I'll change the menu outside.
- Okay.
(In 5th place, they start the 2nd half.)
I'll start the second menu item.
That's right. The second item.
Yes.
At first glance, a half and half bowl makes you think...
it'll give you two dishes that most people would enjoy.
For the second half,
we prepared cold perilla oil pasta.
(Perilla oil makguksu has gone beyond a trend...)
(and became a staple.)
It's a really simple combination.
Soy sauce, sugar, and fragrant perilla oil.
Then we fried dried shrimp and ground them up.
We added a little extra umami.
- You're portioning it individually?
- Yes.
When an order comes in, we can just serve it as is.
That way, the flavor doesn't change.
(Perilla oil sauce portioned out per serving)
(It's used according to the number of orders.)
Then Seok Cheon said,
"It's not just about good food."
"Don't we want people to leave feeling full?"
He's right.
We definitely need some meat.
Pork jowl has a really nice texture.
There's chewiness to its rich fat.
We should serve it with the pasta.
With seasoned perilla leaves,
won't it make the perfect combination?
(Shanghai perilla oil pasta and pork jowl suyuk plate, 13 dollars)
Sprinkle this on the meat at the end.
All right.
- There it is.
- Something changed up there too.
"Shanghai perilla oil pasta?"
(A customer shows interest in the second-half menu.)
(2 customers show interest in the 2nd-half menu.)
(4 customers show interest in the 2nd-half menu.)
It changed to...
- Shanghai perilla oil pasta.
- When did it change?
No way. At this rate, we'll never get out of here.
Let's get perilla oil pasta.
I want the perilla oil pasta.
Perilla oil pasta looks delicious.
Shanghai perilla oil... There's also meat.
(As more customers show interest, a waiting line starts to form.)
Orders are in.
This is Shanghai perilla oil pasta.
Chef, I'll make five at the same time.
The churros aren't ready...
(Park Min Hyuk exclaims.)
(Served alongside the second-half menu item)
(Churros)
When I think of amusement parks, churros and cotton candy are...
some of my fondest childhood memories.
So my focus is on churros.
(Chef Land's second-half strategy: Free churros)
(But the churro dough is still being prepared.)
Orders are coming in, so we need to serve fast.
- Okay.
I was outside wearing an octopus costume.
I could see all the waiting lines.
While food was being served continuously by other teams,
we were at a standstill...
especially in the beginning.
Is everything okay?
- I'll try to be on time.
- Okay.
The orders are piling up. We need to get them out immediately.
If churros aren't ready, serve cotton candy instead.
What's the problem?
If not, let's just go with cotton candy.
Yes.
- Serve cotton candy instead.
- Is that okay with you?
- I want to serve this.
- Churros?
Yes.
You can do it.
None of the orders have gone out yet.
- We have ten orders.
- Right.
Food should be ready...
so that the customers can take it immediately.
I definitely asked him before we started.
"What about the churro dough?"
(During prep)
When will you make the churro dough?
When we're about to finish, I'll start making the dough.
You have to make it right before?
The base is choux pastry, so it has to be made right before frying.
I see.
That's so strange.
Can't he just coat them...
with sugar and have them ready beforehand?
I was starting to get worried.
Seok Cheon, can you make cotton candy?
Let's serve them both.
We just need churros and cotton candy.
- Six dishes are ready.
- Okay.
(Restarting the cotton candy operation)
Orders must go out..
- as fast as possible.
- Okay.
Cotton candy...
Here you go. Hurry.
I'll call the customers now.
Tell them that it's cotton candy instead of churros.
Okay.
We're serving cotton candy instead of churros.
(Replaced by Seok Cheon's cotton candy)
Enjoy your food. Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This cotton candy is free. Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
- Let's keep sending out the orders.
- Okay.
(Staring)
Hoon, if it doesn't work, let's go with cotton candy.
I can make it work.
- You can?
- One batch is...
Give it up fast if it doesn't work.
The speed is important right now.
(Putting the dough into the shaping machine)
We believe in you, Chef Song Hoon.
- I promise to make it work.
- You can do it.
(He finally starts piping out the churros.)
Gosh, why is it so runny?
The churro dough needs...
enough time to be mixed,
cool down, and firm up.
As I rushed it into the shaping machine,
it started getting runny.
Since the dough was already sagging when I fried it,
the churros didn't come out in the right shape.
Hoon, are you okay?
I'll just make cotton candy.
Then take Seok Cheon's place.
Okay.
Could you serve it when I make it?
Instead of shaping it?
That one is ready.
I'm sorry. I should've been more helpful.
Don't say that. We can do it.
You did your best.
(Groaning)
It's not too late.
- It's okay.
The pasta and pork jowl suyuk were...
prepped and ready to go.
So I thought, "We'll be fine."
We have to trust the team.
- Now it's all about speed.
- Let's hurry.
It's all about speed.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
- Cotton candy is ready.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Enjoy your food. We're serving cotton candy instead of churros.
(Remaining servings: 25)
(Remaining servings: 22)
Thank you. Enjoy your food.
(Remaining servings: 17)
I'll serve enough to satisfy Chef Hong.
- Okay.
- I'll serve generously.
Yes, toss it generously.
- Give them plenty.
- It's a double portion.
- Don't skimp.
- Okay.
Call out the order.
- I'll call right away.
- Right away.
- I'll serve it immediately.
- Yes.
Our teamwork is great.
- You're doing well, Chef Land.
- Way to go, Chef Land.
As we got past the halfway point,
the cooking settled into a rhythm.
Without saying much,
we naturally became one team.
Can you hurry up with the cotton candy?
Okay.
Whose idea was it to make cotton candy in the first place?
- Seok Cheon, this is helping us.
- Right.
Here you go.
I served the seasoned perilla leaves, so please take it.
- I'll take it.
- Okay.
This is good.
How many fried tofu rice balls do you add?
Two in each.
We don't have many left to go.
(Global Lunch Box)
We need to make 15 more.
Fifteen? We can do it.
It was less than I expected.
We could sell it all soon.
I thought that we had a chance to win.
- Do you need shrimp?
- Yes.
I'll give it to you now.
- I'll call them now.
- Sure.
You can call them now.
Chef Jun Seong, here you go.
Thank you.
- Did you order one platter?
- Yes.
This is for you.
Order number 3251.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
Thank you.
Here you go. Enjoy your food.
A plate is added to Aunties Kitchen as a penalty.
Don't worry about it.
We don't have many left to go anyway.
Another plate is added...
to Aunties Kitchen as a penalty.
(Current Ranking)
Aunties Kitchen is getting penalized all of a sudden.
(3rd place, Kim Mi Ryeong and Edward Kwon)
(Penalty drops them down the rankings.)
(Fighting for 2nd place with 3 servings apart)
What are they serving anyway?
- How did they get so many?
- I know.
(Sighing)
I'm really sensitive...
about ratings and reviews.
It was a huge blow to my pride.
This menu item required a lot of work.
(A lunch box made of 5 different dishes)
We plate everything ahead of time...
and push it through like a conveyor-belt system.
I think the temperature of the food may have been...
what people found disappointing.
That's what I imagine.
There was a lot of variety, so I didn't get tired of it,
but everything was cold.
All the food is cold.
It's been sitting out for too long.
(There was a variety, but the food was too cold.)
(As expected, the food is criticized for being cold.)
(The cheese in tortilla was hard.)
First, let's take out everything that's been squashed.
- Take it all out?
- Yes.
I thought we should grill it again...
and remake it as quickly as possible.
- The shrimp is ready.
- Okay, I'll take it.
Okay, it's done.
I'll serve each of your platter.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Enjoy your food.
Thank you. Enjoy your food.
All of us are 4 or 5 servings apart.
Let's keep going.
Thank you. Enjoy your food.
I want some ice cream.
The yogurt gelato is 13 dollars.
- We need one more.
- One more.
Hello, it's ready.
What's your order number?
We made this lemon yogurt ice cream from scratch, so you'll like it.
We have about 15 servings left.
Since they haven't announced it yet,
- We're still in the running.
- we're in the running.
This is our final push.
- We can do this.
- Stay strong.
(Only 1 team will survive.)
Someone is making an order.
We expect about three more orders to come in.
Okay. It doesn't matter.
(Ordering)
(Bowing)
(A celebratory dance)
The food will be ready right away.
You'll be served free cotton candy.
It's funny how they're luring people in with cotton candy.
Look, they're luring people.
We have four left.
We need to scoop four more ice creams.
We don't have many left now.
- Did we get four more orders?
- We got quite a lot.
It's fresh gelato made today. Please try it.
Sir, your order will be ready immediately.
(Fighting to survive until the very end)
All right. Someone is making an order.
Your order is ready.
We have our second restaurant...
that sold out all servings.
Chef Land survives after selling out every serving.
(Rushing)
(Jung Ho Young, Song Hoon, Hong Seok Cheon, Park Min Hyuk)
(2nd place, Chef Land survives.)
My gosh.
- It's delicious.
- Isn't it?
It's really good with this.
- Really?
- I like the sauce.
I like this aroma.
The perilla oil aroma is incredible.
- Everything goes well together.
- I know.
How can you get this for just 13 dollars?
This is so good.
If I could find something like this for 13 dollars,
- I'd eat it every day.
- Definitely.
(Without getting any penalty)
(Great texture, nutty, and delicious)
(Great portion and great value, it's simply flawless.)
(They earned a high rating.)
(They started the 2nd half in 5th place.)
(The second-half menu quickly moved them up the rankings.)
The perilla oil dish looks delicious.
(Orders kept pouring in from the start of the second half.)
(From 5th place, they made a comeback to 2nd.)
After the churros problem,
I had pretty much given up.
We felt especially bad because we thought...
we could end up...
hurting Team Goal!
But thankfully, we made it through...
in second place.
You have to admit that you made it through...
because of us.
I'm not as intimidated by you guys anymore.
There will be no more mercy.
With two teams having sold out every single serving,
the 100 serving relay team match is over.
I'm so surprised that we survived!
(1st place, Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon)
(2nd place, Jung Ho Young and Hong Seok Cheon)
My goodness.
Yes!
How can I describe this? It's sad and feels empty.
We lost to the team we were supposed to beat.
It's over.
Once again, I narrowly missed it and ranked third place.
It was so close.
Good job.
- Good job.
You too.
Yes.
Good job.
Let's clean up.
I felt deflated and sorry.
I had a lot of mixed feelings.
Let's go home and take a good rest.
The hard work is over.
The 100 serving relay team match.
The first team to successfully sell all the dishes...
and survive is Kids Restaurant.
(1st place, Kids Restaurant, Choi Sang Hyun and Kim Hoon)
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Nice.
We targeted kids.
They must've made this with kids in mind.
Free cotton candy.
You came here for this, didn't you?
- I'm looking forward to it.
- Me too.
(They place first with the support of kids and parents.)
Congratulations.
The second team to successfully sell all the dishes...
and survive is Chef Land.
(2nd place, Chef Land, Hong Seok Cheon and Jung Ho Young)
(They came from behind in the second half...)
(without receiving a single penalty with Shanghai perilla oil pasta.)
Good job.
Those who failed to sell out are Kim Mi Ryeong,
(Kim Mi Ryeong)
Edward Kwon,
Kim Ho Yoon,
Kim Kwan Hoon,
Go Seok Hyun,
Lee Sung Hoon,
Lee Yeon Bok,
and Kim Min Seong.
- These eight teams...
- What is it?
will be given one last chance to save the business from closing.
Yes!
Please!
They still have one more chance.
"Is there going to be another repechage?"
"I'll go all out."
"I'll win this no matter what."
I was resolute.
I have another chance to survive.
- Please save us.
- Please.
Will be given one last chance.
- Yes!
- What?
- Be happy.
- Let's stop already.
Each team's representative,
please gather in the middle.
The last chance...
to survive.
(The last chance)
A deathmatch.
It's a boss battle.
Boss battle?
(Boss battle)
What?
- What? A boss battle?
- It's a boss battle.
- What's a boss battle?
- We won't be participating.
- A boss battle.
- Now,
the alliance teams are no longer.
My gosh.
Now, you'll go back...
to eight individual restaurants...
and you'll fight each other.
(Completely individual competition)
Two teams will sell in one booth.
(Lulu Land)
Two kiosks will be placed per booth.
(Order here)
The stoves and kitchen utensils...
are to be used upon agreements between the restaurants.
Out of 8 restaurants, only the first 3 teams to sell 30 plates...
will survive.
The boss battle will also add...
penalty plates.
(Penalty plates will be added with customer dissatisfaction.)
The plate to be used for the boss battle is...
what everyone has avoided.
The cauldron-shaped bowl?
It's the cauldron-shaped bowl.
(Everyone avoided using it.)
- Not this.
- This is hard.
It's hard to use it.
I thought the bowl was really difficult to make use of.
Seven sections?
Can I utilize them all?
The sales price is 11 dollars for every team.
We don't have ingredients left.
Also, eight additional ingredients are ready for you.
They have more ingredients.
Each person can choose...
one ingredient.
- Team leaders, - Open 1 by 1.
- please choose your ingredient.
- This.
- Ham, chicken.
- Shrimps. I'm sick of them.
Eggs, ham, and beef loin.
Boneless drumsticks.
Fried chicken in hot and sour soy sauce or spicy garlic fried chicken?
We still have shrimps left.
Yes.
I haven't thought of the menu yet.
I chose the ingredient first and thought about it later.
Shall we take potatoes?
Because we have chicken.
Take the potatoes.
(Extra ingredients selection)
(Lee Yeon Bok: Chicken, Kim Min Seong: Squid,)
(Go Seok Hyun: Shrimp, Lee Sung Hoon: Eggs,)
(Kim Ho Yoon: Canned ham, Kim Kwan Hoon: Beef loin)
You have two hours to prepare.
One hour before the business starts...
Good luck.
Only the team leaders will remain...
- to prepare for the business.
- We can do it.
Don't worry.
The boss battle begins...
at 6:30pm.
You could become enemies who eliminate each other...
or comrades who survive together.
Please start preparing for business.
Good luck.
- Good luck.
How will two teams share?
Chef, I'm sorry you're going through all this trouble because of us.
- Why would you say that?
- I'm sorry.
- As I said first, - Don't say that.
I tried my best not to cause a nuisance.
But it has come to this. I'm sorry.
You never know what might happen.
I'm sorry.
I'll stir-fry it...
I acted fine, but...
We were leading in first place.
In sixth place, Wandering Panda.
- We're in last place.
We experienced the two extremes.
I'll survive no matter what.
I won't just survive.
I'll win first place.
That's how I can save face.
It's my pride.
Can you pass me the bowl?
The eight-section bowl?
(Sucking his teeth)
The bowl is the problem.
When they'd announced the cauldron-shaped bowl,
they said we didn't need to use the top part of the plate.
When I think about it,
most people won't use the top plate.
"So I'll make use of this somehow."
That was the first thought I had.
You don't need to make multiple dishes for it.
- But...
- You can cook some chicken...
- and...
the food in the middle is the bait.
Sorry?
It's better to use it.
- Really?
- You can lure the customers.
There are many empty spaces.
I wanted to fill them up, just a bit for each at least.
Not many chefs would be able to fill it up.
I'll bring out the most of my skills.
I'll fill up the eight sections.
Two sections each.
(4 more dishes to make)
I'll make as many dishes as I can.
(4 side dishes, 1 main dish)
(He'll make 5 dishes in total.)
The customers will look at the price and go,
"This food for this price?"
That's my strategy.
(His strategy is to be cost-effective.)
The ingredients are the problem.
It won't be easy to do with the remaining ingredients.
(They can get ingredients from the surviving teams.)
These are all perilla leaves.
You could season it.
(Perilla leaves)
- The sauce to season it with.
- This?
You can use this.
Do you have garlic?
This is celtuce.
Celtuce? Nice.
I got celtuce from Chef Ho Young.
What they had left.
(Impromptu cooking 1: Seasoned celtuce and onion)
It'd be nice if we had pickled radish...
to put in the middle as a side dish.
It will help with the greasiness.
(The next impromptu cooking to fill up the sections around it)
We had some meat left from tangsuyuk.
"Let's make tangsuyuk again."
- It will go in here.
- Yes.
- Cut it small.
Tangsuyuk won't fit on the plate...
if the meat is too big.
So we cut it into small pieces.
And we deep-fried the small pieces.
(Impromptu cooking 2: Mini tangsuyuk)
I opened the chicken box.
"Let's add something to it." That's what I thought.
(Soy sauce chicken: Chicken, sugar, soy sauce)
(Pepper)
(Potato starch)
Mix them well so they're coated evenly.
Press them hard so the starch sticks.
(Impromptu cooking 3: Soy sauce chicken)
And one more.
We had a lot of shrimps,
so I decided to use them.
I made cream and cooked cream shrimps.
(Add handmade cream sauce to boiled shrimps.)
It's an imperial family set.
Use bulgogi, onions, and Chinese noodles.
I thought I might as well make jjajangmyeon.
So I made jjajang bulgogi.
It's turning into jjajang bulgogi.
Nice.
I should be charging 15 dollars...
just for the jjajangmyeon.
(Impromptu cooking 5: Beef bulgogi jjajangmyeon)
You can't buy beef bulgogi jjajangmyeon...
with 11 dollars.
But it has fried chicken, tangsuyuk, and cream shrimps...
on top of it.
I wanted them to think it'd be their loss if they missed out.
It's a strategy too.
(Bulgogi Jjajangmyeon Set, good value for 11 dollars)
(Kim Ho Yoon right after the boss battle announcement)
What ingredients do you have left?
We have boiled pasta noodles...
I ran to Kids Restaurant immediately.
They won first place, which means...
their food tasted good, for one,
and they must've prepared their ingredients well.
(He visits Kids Restaurant first.)
- I'll take the pasta noodles.
- He approached me first.
- Really?
- I'll take jambon.
(Jambon)
Ragu sauce.
I'll use whipped cream.
(Whipped cream)
I took as many remaining ingredients as I could.
Can I take this?
We don't know.
I said I'd take it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Shall we share half each?
- Half? This should be enough.
- Okay.
Okay, good.
Okay.
(Carrying the whole basket)
(His next target is Chef Land.)
How much...
How much do you have left? Perilla leaves? Did they take them?
We have a bit left.
He's taking everything.
(Various condiments)
(Ho Yoon came back to his booth with both hands full.)
Let's start planning the menu in ten minutes.
(Tons of ingredients he got from the other teams)
There's nothing much to prepare now. This is my strategy, Chan Hee.
Perilla leaves, pasta noodles, and steak.
Steak pasta with medium-cooked steak.
Whoever sells out first wins.
If you sell steak pasta...
at 11 dollars, that would stand out.
I decided to cook steak rose pasta.
Do I stir-fry ham and onions in chili oil?
Yes.
(He makes the pasta sauce using canned ham, the extra ingredient.)
(He adds the ragu sauce from the Kids Restaurant too.)
We only need to sell 30 plates.
So the singularity.
How to make it witty.
I kept thinking about it.
I want to place it nicely on the bowl.
Side dishes to go with it.
They said you didn't need to use the sections.
Yes.
We don't need to, but we could.
You need to cook everything yourself for the boss battle.
So I was sure nobody would use...
the seven-section plate.
(Out of the boss battle participants,)
(only Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Ho Yoon...)
(used the 7-section plates.)
I ensured...
the seven-section plate will contain...
various preferences, textures, tastes, and flavors.
In the middle is fried chicken with chicken we brined ourselves,
and on the side are chopped pistachios.
- This should be enough, right?
- It has to.
And we made croutons...
with squid ink baguette which was prepared for mianbao xia.
(Squid ink baguette crouton)
And perilla oil sauce.
(Perilla oil sauce)
I added some perilla leaves.
(Perilla leaf sprouts)
Jambon.
Grated cheese.
I named it the night picnic.
(Top blade rose pasta and night picnic set)
(Perilla leaf sprout, fried chicken, squid ink baguette crouton,)
(perilla oil sauce, cheese, jambon, chopped pistachios)
(A total of 7 side dishes)
When they're about to get sick of eating pasta,
they can have something crispy,
something strong-flavored and fresh like perilla leaf sprouts,
or cheese to make the taste richer.
Perilla oil will taste good in its own way too.
It's like a wine platter...
in an amusement park.
(Beef loin, top blade steak)
I thought I'd have the advantage since the sales price is the same.
- I'll use it for a while.
- Sure.
- I just need to heat it up.
- Go ahead.
- It's done.
- Feel free to use.
Done.
(Kwan Hoon is already done with his preparation.)
I'm cooking...
tteokbokki again.
I had a clear topic in mind, and I only wanted to do tteokbokki.
Even if I may fail proudly.
With tteokbokki...
Tteokbokki is the only thing I can cook.
Let's reinterpret tteokbokki in a fun and interesting way...
using the ingredients I have.
I don't need to measure it.
Just do what your gut tells you.
I need to create something from nothing.
(Kim Kwan Hoon's previous menu)
(Bouquet fritters and honey garlic fried rice cake)
(The only main ingredient)
(Rice cake)
Firstly...
We don't have any other ingredients we can use, right?
I needed to do something, and I needed any ingredient.
I visited all the booths...
and took everything I needed.
Do you have a lot of onions?
- Onions are...
- Or any vegetables.
I've got a lot of green onions.
Can I have a lot, please?
Amazing.
Thank you. We don't have any vegetables.
Hurrah!
All I need are green onions.
Green onions are a must for tteokbokki.
I got green onions.
(Green onions and onions make him dance.)
It's my strength.
I make use of what little ingredients I have.
And we don't really...
become intimidated.
We're happy and positive.
(What's today's tteokbokki made by the extremely positive king?)
We have shrimps and squids left.
Shrimps, squids, tteokbokki, and perilla leaves.
I'll make land-sea-air tteokbokki...
and stick all the remaining fritters.
I considered how I had a lot of shrimps and squids.
This is too much.
This is a rice cake shop.
(Adding the special sauce of Everything About Tteokbokki)
I put in meat...
to add the zest.
I made the soup taste stronger.
(Slurping)
(Confused)
Why does this taste good?
This is fascinating. Why does it taste good?
Make it very red.
It's dinnertime,
so they might crave spicy food.
It'll get cold.
(While tteokbokki is boiled down to become spicy...)
There's not enough time to cook everything by himself.
(Fried chicken as lean as grilled chicken)
I deep-fried it all...
so he can set it with tteokbokki,
and I left.
Maybe it could actually work out well.
(Place shrimps, squids, and chicken fritters.)
It looked like we had a chance.
(Land-sea-air tteokbokki, beef loin)
(Land-sea-air tteokbokki, shrimps and squids)
(Land-sea-air tteokbokki, fried chicken)
(Land-sea-air tteokbokki)
I didn't expect this at all.
Seok Hyun, let us both survive.
We can do it.
- We're still one.
- We are!
- One!
Again! We are!
Tae Hee can help with futomaki.
We turned from an alliance to competitors.
But we decided to help each other like we're in a team...
and survive together.
Since I brought a kiln anyway,
let's make Tendon again just like the last round.
It's one of the dishes I'm most confident in.
(Special mixed tendon by Lee Sung Hoon)
I wanted to put something new...
on futomaki.
(Big cream shrimps and futomaki by Go Seok Hyun)
(Lulu Land, 11 dollars)
If you're not a team leader,
please head to the monitoring room.
- Good luck.
Good luck. Good luck, Chef.
(All the teammates leave before the business starts.)
- Show them.
- We'll survive.
Okay.
- Bye, Sung Hoon.
- Bye.
(Turning around in regret)
All the best.
Good luck.
Taste it to make your decision.
(The son has a hard time leaving.)
- Bye.
Wear your reading glasses and manage the POS well.
- I will.
- Anything you don't know, ask him.
(Can't leave until the end)
Friend, go and rest.
I'll face this head-on.
I came all the way here. I must survive.
My heart raced, but I was confident.
I thought I had a high chance at survival again.
Cooking isn't hard for me.
I'm confident.
I'll show them.
I'm confident. I'll survive.
- Good luck.
- You can do it.
(The survivors and the teammates will watch in the situation room.)
An individual match is interesting.
It's about their pride.
It makes my heart pound.
This is a lot more thrilling than the World Soccer Games.
The deathmatch,
the boss battle, starts now.
I want to eat quickly.
I'm hungry.
(The customers who'll decide their fates enter.)
I can't wait to find out.
It smells good.
(They can order from 4 stalls.)
(They can order 8 menus.)
(The new dishes freshly printed out and put up)
Let's do this.
(Out of the 8 bosses...)
(Edward Kwon, Kim Mi Ryeong, Lee Yeon Bok, Kim Min Seong...)
(They need to sell 30 plates as fast as they can.)
- Enjoy.
(Only 3 will survive.)
It's all covered up.
Let's go.
- Do we just order?
- What shall we eat?
Who will receive the first order?
(Which boss will get the first order of the boss battle?)
(After scanning the menus from her seat, she stands up.)
(Edward Kwon and Kim Mi Ryeong)
Shall we have one?
(Surprised)
(Inside, two bosses are waiting for the order.)
- They got something.
- They got it.
(Finished ordering)
They'll send us a notification.
(Who got the first order?)
Nice.
(The first order goes to Edward Kwon.)
I got an order.
I got an order!
(What menu did Edward Kwon prepare that captured the first customer?)
(A while ago, during the preparation time)
I just need to boil this.
After making tomato salad,
we had a lot of pasta noodles left.
(Short pasta for tomato salad)
I'd cooked it al dente,
so I could turn this...
into pasta.
At the same time, as it's an amusement park,
I thought the customers would like meat.
That was why I chose pork shoulder.
I made cuts in the pork shoulder...
and used galbi sauce to give it that Korean cuisine taste.
After marinating it for a bit, I grilled the meat.
I cut it once it cooled down a bit...
to help it keep its shape.
(A combination of tomato pasta and pork galbi)
(Topping it off with grilled shrimp)
Inside are seafood,
meat, and carbs.
I saw Young Min's eyes.
It gave me certainty.
- Did I give you that look?
- Yes. I saw it in your eyes.
(Signaling with his eyes)
Didn't I suddenly turn taciturn?
- Yes, you did.
- Right?
He didn't talk, but there was fire in his eyes.
In a way, it's a fusion dish.
Shrimp tomato pasta with pork shoulder galbi.
(Edward Kwon: Shrimp tomato pasta with marinated pork shoulder)
- Pork shoulder.
- Hey.
- Pork shoulder?
(Edward Kwon: 3 orders)
- What should we get?
- Chicken and pasta?
- Both look good.
- Which one?
Pork shoulders marinated in galbi sauce.
How about pasta?
- On the left?
- Yes.
- I'm in.
- Here's your pasta.
- Great.
Enjoy.
Take both. Thank you.
What's this?
This one is...
shrimp tomato pasta.
The shrimp tomato pasta is good.
It's my kind of food.
The pasta was made with short noodles.
It's different from usual pasta.
It has a kick to it, right?
Kind of Korean-like.
Korean flavors have been added to it.
It suits the Korean taste buds.
- True.
- It gets a perfect score.
(Edward Kwon: Shrimp tomato pasta)
(The orders keep coming in.)
(Orders keep flooding in.)
What?
(Even with orders rushing in)
(Pasta kept warm after cooking)
(Pre-prepared toppings)
(A dish that can go out with minimal movement)
Okay.
He's super fast.
Here's your pasta. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Have a pleasant dinner.
Young Min is really calm when working alone,
but when cooking together, he's such a nagger.
That's him.
- I worked with him for 11 years.
- Right?
How many did you serve, Chef?
A lot, right?
About 12 or 13 orders.
That's my guess.
(Edward Kwon: 12 orders, Kim Mi Ryeong: Not defined yet)
Did the others serve a lot too?
(The restaurant next to Aunties Kitchen)
There's even jjajangmyeon.
Should we get steak?
Mom, order jjajangmyeon.
(Ordered 1 jjajangmyeon meal)
We must survive, sir.
Let's both survive!
The start has to be good.
For real.
(Lee Yeon Bok: 1 out of 30 orders)
- You have an order.
- Let's do this.
Order's up!
It's bulgogi jjajang stir-fry and tangsuyuk.
- Do you want bulgogi stir-fry?
- Yes.
All set.
(The young customers' top choice is jjajangmyeon.)
(Bulgogi jjajang stir-fried noodles and tangsuyuk meal)
Did I get three orders altogether?
(Lee Yeon Bok: 4 out of 30 orders)
(Kim Min Seong: 1 out of 30 orders)
Let's go.
(Both start cooking their first order.)
(Cooking the jjajangmyeon)
(Tangsuyuk and soy sauce chicken)
(When he is about to plate the noodles)
Here it is.
(Kim Min Seong's menu is served in no time.)
Gosh, it's... You're really fast.
(Kim Min Seong's menu is built to win on speed.)
(Ragu gratin soup with croffle)
(When the order comes in)
(Bottom: Scrambled eggs)
(Middle: Ragu gratin soup)
(Top: Croffles)
(Wrapping it up with cheese)
Take your ragu meal!
(Served fast with a simple combination)
(One table has ordered the ragu and croffle meal.)
Mom, what's the name of this one?
That one? It's ragu gratin soup with croffle.
- Is the croffle the best?
- Yes.
- Wandering Panda?
- Right?
Is it the best dish?
- I want to try this.
- Right?
Even the eggs are good.
Mom, can you order another after I finish this?
Should I order another one?
Please order another waffle.
- Tell me after you finish it.
- Okay.
(The kids love it. The croffle is good.)
(10 minutes into business)
- Good.
- Did you order one?
(Customers crowd over at Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong's.)
(Order showdown: Ragu with croffle versus Jjajang with tangsuyuk)
What a bang for the buck.
Look at the portion size.
It's 11 dollars.
(Ordered 1 jjajang meal)
(Picked for its good value for money)
- Order whichever you'd like.
- What do they have?
Whatever you're craving.
- Bulgogi jjajang?
- Okay.
(Ordered 1 jjajang meal)
(Picked by the young customer)
- Let's have that one.
- Pasta.
- These two.
- It's ragu and jjajang.
I'm hungry.
Isn't this jjajangmyeon?
Check your phone, okay?
(Ordered 1 jjajang meal, Picked for dinner)
- The jjajang is selling.
- Right?
Totally.
Customers must love noodles.
Here's the tangsuyuk meal.
Please take it after checking the order number.
What's this?
(Sighing)
Goodness.
(The orders come rushing in,)
(but only 4 orders have been served.)
If I didn't change my strategy,
it was going to be tough. That was what crossed my mind.
(Mass production begins.)
- Gosh.
- Five in one go?
Six.
He's everywhere. Look.
After putting the noodles in, he takes out the fritters.
Six.
(Finished 6 orders in a flash)
That's 11 dollars?
What a packed menu.
Chef Lee Yeon Bok is going all out.
Here's your bulgogi jjajang meal.
Your tangsuyuk meal is ready.
Please take it after checking the order number.
Take the one with your order number.
Thank you.
(Lee Yeon Bok served 10 orders.)
(Other customers are interested after seeing the crowd.)
Tangsuyuk and stir-fried noodles are the best, no questions asked.
(Ordered 1 jjajang)
(Another order)
(15 out of 30 orders)
(Reached 50 percent)
Currently in the leading group are...
Edward Kwon and Lee Yeon Bok.
The 2 are competing with a 3-order difference.
Wandering Panda is already serving.
Bulgogi rice bowl.
- For dinner?
- Yes.
I see.
(The customers walk by Ho Yoon and Kwan Hoon's restaurant.)
(One chef is getting anxious.)
(And the other chef is calm.)
(Kim Kwan Hoon: 0 orders, Kim Ho Yoon: 0 orders)
- There's only one.
- Top blade steak?
- Or the picnic set?
- It's all out here.
- Let's get the picnic set.
- Okay.
- Only 30 are available.
- Is that so?
(Top blade rose pasta and night picnic set, 30 limited orders)
We're getting an order. Whose will it be first?
It could be yours, sir.
(Kwan Hoon)
Nice.
- Pasta.
- Okay.
(The first order is for Ho Yoon.)
(Starting by cooking the portioned pasta noodles)
(Kim Kwan Hoon: 0 orders, Kim Ho Yoon: 2 orders)
Nice.
(Kwan Hoon gets his first order not long after.)
(Kim Kwan Hoon: 1 order, Kim Ho Yoon: 2 orders)
(Kim Kwan Hoon: 2 orders, Kim Ho Yoon: 2 orders)
You're getting orders. Nice, tteokbokki!
Let's go, tteokbokki!
- Good luck to both of us.
- Good luck.
(For one order of tteokbokki to be served)
(Scooping some tteokbokki)
(Top it off with fritters, and it's done.)
(Served 2 orders in just 1 minute)
I want to try the tteokbokki.
Should we order one?
(Kim Kwan Hoon: 3 orders)
How about we try the land-sea-air tteokbokki?
(Kim Kwan Hoon: 4 orders)
When it comes to speed...
I'm fast at everything.
Enjoy.
This here is the tteokbokki.
Take the order under your number.
The pre-scooped tteokbokki is served right away.
As always, the greatest strategy in this boss battle is...
speed.
(Kwan Hoon has no outstanding orders yet.)
(Glancing)
Gosh, look at the orders.
He's taking too long.
Plating 2 servings is taking over 3 minutes.
(Kim Ho Yoon: 8 orders)
(Only 2 out of 8 orders have been served.)
I had to serve quickly as it was a battle of speed.
(For one order to be served)
(Cooking the pasta)
(Cooking the beef loin)
There were too many details.
(Cooking the steak)
I even had to place the sectioned plate on the top.
(Plating)
The dishwashing had to be done while I was cooking.
(Washing the pan)
Be careful when you carry it.
That one?
Let's try the top blade.
Night picnic meal!
Look at that one.
Top blade steak rose pasta.
(Customers gather after spotting the top blade steak.)
Once the pasta noodles...
go into the pan, they start becoming soggy.
Even that has what's called a golden timing.
I had no time to look around at all.
Which one is the top blade steak?
The steak will be ready soon.
- Is it not done yet?
- No.
Stay calmer, yet serve a higher quality dish.
All I could do was take it slow, one at a time.
Hi.
Please take your order. Take one, please.
Selling 30 orders won't be easy.
I totally agree.
(Kwan Hoon takes Ho Yoon's pan.)
- Hey.
- Yes?
- I washed your pan. Use it.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Good.
(Kwan Hoon washed Ho Yoon's pan.)
When the orders come in together,
I'd be serving 2 to 3 while Ho Yoon serves 1.
I had nothing to do.
But Ho Yoon was all over the place and right next to me at that.
(Staring)
(The pan washer is on the move.)
I ladled the tteokbokki quite nonchalantly.
But helping him was fun.
I had nothing to do, and I was rooting for him too.
Here, your pan.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
(Even helping out with the meat)
Thank you.
(Even helping out with the pasta)
Do we have no scissors?
- Scissors?
- Yes.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
But I have nothing to do.
After all, my orders are served right away.
- I'm not trying to use you.
- Here are your scissors.
Thank you.
How kind of you.
(How kind of you.)
A big-hearted person.
No other words are needed. He's a big-hearted person.
I want to be like him as a businessman.
Hi. You may take your order.
Take one, please.
CEO Kwan Hoon helped me quite a lot.
(Kim Ho Yoon, Orders: 14, Served: 6)
Take one, please.
(Kim Ho Yoon, Orders: 14, Served: 8)
Go and cook your dishes.
- Okay.
- I've got plenty of time.
Currently in the leading group are...
Edward Kwon,
Lee Yeon Bok,
Kim Ho Yoon...
Kim Ho Yoon.
Let's go, Young Min!
- Kim Ho Yoon!
- Ho Yoon.
And Lee Sung Hoon.
- Lee Sung Hoon.
- Lee Sung Hoon?
(Lee Sung Hoon's partner)
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Two first.
- Okay, two first.
(Lee Sung Hoon, Special mixed tendon: 16 orders)
A total of... It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- Ten orders.
- Okay.
I'm skipping the bills.
Currently at the bottom in sales is...
Kim Mi Ryeong.
(Currently at the bottom in sales is Kim Mi Ryeong.)
Imokase is taking a break too long.
You're right. No orders are coming in.
What was the menu again?
The name is Chinese-style chicken rice bowl.
- Chinese-style chicken rice bowl?
Chicken, potato, and fried rice.
Let's top it off with boneless braised spicy chicken.
- Make it spicy?
- Yes.
From what I see, we need to make it very flavorful.
(Kim Mi Ryeong's boss battle menu)
(Chinese-style chicken rice bowl)
I didn't get a single order while everyone else had a line.
One, two, three.
After that, there were none.
Honestly, I was totally lost.
(Edward Kwon:19 orders, Kim Mi Ryeong: 7 orders)
What if I come in last? That'll be embarrassing.
I kept looking outside...
and walking around.
(Strolling around out of anxiousness)
The machine isn't broken, is it?
(Glancing)
Why isn't she getting any orders?
- It's suddenly getting windy.
- Right?
It's cold all of a sudden.
When I was thinking,
"There's a slight wind,"
"so why isn't that menu selling?"
What was the menu again?
Chinese-style chicken rice bowl.
- Chinese-style chicken rice bowl?
- Yes.
Can you change the name of the menu?
Or no?
It's the name.
The name seems like the problem here.
A menu's name can make all the difference.
Customers usually associate the name...
with the menu right away.
When they do,
the taste and the preference must match.
Order complete.
Shrimp tomato pasta with marinated pork shoulder.
That menu is likely to get chosen.
There needs to be a hook.
The "Chinese" part...
may make the customers think of regular egg fried rice.
We should add "fried rice" to it.
- Exactly.
- "I can't go home..."
"without selling any." That was what I thought.
(Chinese-style chicken rice bowl)
Shrimp and chicken fried rice with Auntie's spicy braised chicken.
The customers will associate with that name almost immediately.
I should've chosen a different menu.
No. You never know once the name changes.
Maybe.
Come on. I'm biased toward my own.
We're a family.
I wanted Chef Kim Mi Ryeong to advance with me.
See that place with the arch?
(The customer is about to order Edward Kwon's menu.)
Wait. It's changing to braised spicy chicken.
Should we get that instead?
Rather than pasta...
(Kim Mi Ryeong, Edward Kwon)
Fried rice?
Names are important.
(Ordering Kim Mi Ryeong's menu instead of Edward Kwon's)
Braised spicy chicken sounds good too.
Right?
Which one?
Here's your order.
It's your order. The name of the menu changed.
After that,
the orders came in...
- one after the other.
- Enjoy. Don't forget your drink.
The name of the menu changed.
Is that so? Where?
It used to be Chinese-style chicken rice bowl.
Shall we dig in?
It looks a lot like braised spicy chicken.
(The customer ordered it when it was Chinese-style chicken rice bowl.)
The image we had of it was different from what was served.
You're right about that.
So it was braised spicy chicken.
The orders are coming in with the new menu.
I told you.
That's what you call business.
(Lee Yeon Bok and Kim Min Seong)
(Meanwhile, Lee Yeon Bok is busy as ever.)
Oh, dear.
(Entire batch of tangsuyuk is lost.)
(Shocked)
What is it?
- The pre-fried tangsuyuk.
- No way.
- What now?
- There's none, right?
What now? He's lost it.
(Shocked)
Seriously.
I dropped the tangsuyuk.
How many do you have left?
(The remaining tangsuyuk is...)
(2 servings which he was frying.)
Gosh, I just dropped the tangsuyuk.
(Many orders came in,)
(but none can be served.)
- The ingredients...
- He needs to deep-fry it again.
There's none.
He has to serve without it.
But there's already a picture of it.
- The picture.
- Yes.
If it went wrong, he could get a penalty.
(Tangsuyuk)
(Tangsuyuk is included in the menu name.)
(He decides to make it again.)
I was worried about getting a penalty,
so I just made tangsuyuk again.
I was in such a rush.
It would delay things even further.
(Pouring the batter mixture all over again)
(At least 10 minutes until completion)
(That means he will fall behind on orders.)
I thought that if it went at this pace and orders piled up,
I would fall completely behind.
(Number of orders)
(Number of orders: 20, 20, 17, 19)
(Number of dishes served)
(Number of dishes served: 14, 12, 15, 15)
(Yeon Bok is in 4th place.)
(Yeon Bok is on the verge of elimination.)
(Yeon Bok's 7-sectioned plate)
I'll do it. You can work on the other things.
Let me do it.
- Oh, dear.
- I'm on it.
We were one team.
Watching it without helping would make me less than human.
The whole thing happened because of me.
He could not advance because of me.
I wanted to help.
At least one of us should advance.
I was really grateful that he helped with my work.
Listen. For now...
You have 23 orders now.
Don't worry about the 23 orders for now.
Just keep pushing orders out.
You can just keep going like this.
All right.
(Min Seong helps with Yeon Bok's orders.)
(Filling up the trays, making tangsuyuk)
(Cooperative play)
It looks like he's helping.
Yes. Min Seong is helping him.
He got a job at Yeon Bok's restaurant.
It's beautiful.
(While the new batch of tangsuyuk is frying,)
(Min Seong is doing the final plating for jjajangmyeon.)
(The jjajangmyeon factory is operating at full capacity.)
We can't send it out because of tangsuyuk.
(Yeon Bok and Min Seong are working as one team.)
(The tangsuyuk is done.)
One moment, please. We will give you the jjajang soon.
It's coming up soon.
- Can I take this?
- Yes. You can take them first.
Here's your bulgogi jjajang.
(Thanks to his teammate's great performance,)
(Lee Yeon Bok has completed 15 orders.)
You can check your number and take it.
You can take it. Thank you.
(Lee Yeon Bok has completed 19 orders.)
- That was seven orders, right?
- Yes.
- We need to send out more dishes.
- Currently, Lee Yeon Bok...
- has overtaken...
- Here's your bulgogi jjajang.
Edward Kwon.
What's with Chef Yeon Bok?
He's a true professional. He managed it somehow.
He's really cool. That's Chef Lee Yeon Bok.
And Min Seong is helping him.
It's possible because of his help.
This is awesome.
Maybe we should give him an achievement award or something.
He finally came to his senses.
Now he puts perilla leaves on top.
They put something on the bulgogi jjajang?
That's...
- Perilla leaves.
- Like coastal hog fennel.
- That was ours.
You wanted to eat jjajang.
(Beef bulgogi jjajangmyeon topped with perilla leaves)
I like how it has perilla leaves on top.
The tangsuyuk is the real deal here.
- Good.
- I mean it. Try it.
(A bite of freshly fried tangsuyuk)
- This is good.
- I know, right?
- It's delicious.
- Is this onion?
(Changing the bowls)
(Exclaiming)
- It's good, isn't it?
- This is good.
It's delicious.
It goes well with perilla leaves.
I know. It tastes good.
The perilla leaves are a stroke of genius here.
(The tangsuyuk was the best, and the perilla leaves were great.)
Do you like it?
The tangsuyuk is crispy,
and the jjajangmyeon is tasty.
It is a fantastic flavor.
Mom, the jjajangmyeon is great. You should try it.
Try this.
Try the jjajangmyeon.
(Yeon Bok's jjajangmyeon is popular with people of all ages.)
Currently in first place is...
(30 minutes into the boss battle)
(Edward Kwon, shrimp tomato pasta with marinated pork shoulder)
(Kim Ho Yoon, top blade rose pasta and night picnic meal)
(Lee Yeon Bok, bulgogi jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk meal)
(Lee Sung Hoon, special mixed tendon)
(Among the 4 chefs in the lead,)
(who is currently in 1st place?)
It's Lee Sung Hoon.
(Lee Sung Hoon)
The tendon.
- Tendon.
- Really?
Good.
(Surprised)
It's tendon.
- Koony.
- It's been quiet.
I was only looking at the other three places.
It's unbelievable.
Lee Sung Hoon.
(Lee Sung Hoon takes 1st place in the interim results.)
Let's go.
Just win. Don't worry about me.
No. We need to win together.
I just thought I needed to clear the orders quickly.
- I pressed the bell.
- Okay. Thank you.
Since my role was handling the POS, plating neatly, drizzling sauce,
and sending out food,
it was more work than expected.
I thought I should carry out those roles well.
(Lee Sung Hoon has 5 orders left.)
Lee Sung Hoon.
A plate is added to Lee Sung Hoon as a penalty.
I get a penalty right away like this?
(Lee Sung Hoon has 5 orders left.)
(Lee Sung Hoon has 6 orders left.)
I think you need to taste the food.
What is it? Is it because of the rice?
Am I doing something wrong right now?
Am I frying something wrong?
Did we get a call for the tendon?
No, we haven't.
Two servings of shrimp, please.
(Just like earlier today, fried food orders start piling up.)
- Shrimp for futomaki.
- Shrimp for futomaki. I got it.
(He even fried food for two menu items all by himself.)
Is the fried shrimp done yet?
- I'm desperate.
- It's coming out soon.
(A waiting line forms.)
Tendon? Shall we order tendon?
(Meanwhile, 1 order is added.)
Since it is fried on the spot, it does take time.
- Earlier...
- Tendon?
This is why...
they took orders quickly, but finished later than we did.
This is the reason.
(Lee Sung Hoon has 2 orders left.)
How many dishes did you order?
Lee Sung Hoon.
A plate is added to Lee Sung Hoon as a penalty.
Okay. Did you order one?
- Enjoy it.
- With this,
Kim Ho Yoon has turned the tables.
(Kim Ho Yoon takes the lead by a single order.)
- Thank you. Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy it.
- Yes!
- Ho Yoon takes the lead.
This really is a series of plot twists.
- We can do this.
- All right.
(Lee Sung Hoon has 2 orders left.)
Here is steak pasta.
Go and work.
(Kim Ho Yoon has 1 order left.)
Let's go.
(Lee Sung Hoon has 1 order left.)
It's coming out soon.
One order each.
(They both have 1 order left each.)
(Lulu Land)
- Futomaki.
- Tendon?
It's 30 top blade steaks. Is this the same thing?
I don't know. I am going to try ordering this for now.
(Who will be the 1st to get 30 orders?)
Kim Ho Yoon...
has received 30 orders.
He received the orders.
However, survival is only secured...
once the last dish goes out to the customer.
(Survival is confirmed only after the 30th dish is served.)
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
You can eat it together with the pasta or separately.
(Kim Ho Yoon: 30 orders)
(Kim Ho Yoon: 7 orders to serve)
He just needs to finish those quickly now.
Five.
(And 1 minute later)
Lee Sung Hoon...
has received 30 orders.
Let's do this. Focus.
(Lee Sung Hoon, Orders: 30, Served: 17)
- We can do this.
- All right.
(He will survive once he serves 13 orders.)
- Thank you. Enjoy it.
- Enjoy it.
I think Lee Sung Hoon will take 1st, Ho Yoon 2nd,
and Yeon Bok third.
(Currently in the middle of a fierce ranking battle)
Please take your drinks.
(Yeon Bok is currently in 3rd place.)
Orders for Lee Yeon Bok have surpassed 27 dishes.
You can take it right away.
Food will keep coming out.
Here's your food.
Whoever arrives first may take it.
(Lee Yeon Bok, Orders: 27, Served: 19)
(Orders were backed up because of the tangsuyuk.)
(While frying meat,)
(he boils noodles.)
It's ready.
(Pouring jjajang)
(The menu item is complete only after pouring the sauce.)
Chef Yeon Bok moves...
- incredibly fast.
- I know.
He's really fast.
Usually, after serving about ten dishes,
I get the hang of it.
I get a feel for how to do things.
Before that, he was a little flustered,
wondering what to do first.
(Waiting)
(Early on, the timing for each dish was off.)
As Yeon Bok picked up speed,
the timing synced perfectly when adding the noodles later.
I thought, "It's fine now. He got the hang of it now."
(Finishing up the frying right after plating the noodles)
Once I get used to it, everything smooths out completely.
(Outside at that moment)
- Are you ready to pay?
- It looks like...
the orders are closed.
(Lee Yeon Bok's menu is sold out.)
Lee Yeon Bok has received 30 orders.
I need to send the food out quickly and turn the tables.
Currently in first place is Kim Ho Yoon,
with six orders left to serve until survival.
Awesome.
Good job!
(Kim Ho Yoon: 6 orders to serve, Lee Sung Hoon: Not defined yet)
The question is who sends the food out faster.
I bet the tendon will take first place.
It's between Kim Ho Yoon and Lee Sung Hoon.
Neck-and-neck.
- I'm sending out three at a time.
- Okay.
- Thank you. Enjoy it.
- Enjoy it.
(Sighing)
Enjoy your meal.
We have the first survivor who achieved...
30 orders sold in the boss battle.
- The first survivor is...
- Kim Ho Yoon.
Is it Lee Sung Hoon?
(Who is the first survivor of the boss battle?)
Lee Yeon Bok.
Please move to the Survival Room immediately.
(Surprised)
He must've unlocked his potential.
It's unbelievable.
Just as expected.
Lee Yeon Bok.
Please move to the Survival Room immediately.
(When the 30th order came in)
(Yeon Bok had already finished the dishes to go out in advance.)
(Jajang was served the moment orders come in.)
Surpassing 28 dishes.
Two remaining. We have two orders left.
(Skillfully clearing the final two orders)
- It's done, right?
- Yes, it's all done.
(Lee Yeon Bok, Orders: 30, Served: 29)
Please take your food matching your ticket number.
Please take your drinks.
(Lee Yeon Bok, Orders: 30, Served: 30)
Done.
(Completely sold out in 1 minute after reaching 30 orders)
The first survivor is...
Lee Yeon Bok.
What a twist.
I'm so relieved.
- My goodness.
- It's unbelievable.
- Good work.
- Just as expected from him.
Lee Yeon Bok.
Chef Lee Yeon Bok.
Yes!
(The first survivor of the boss battle: Lee Yeon Bok)
(He survived only in 50 minutes.)
This feels really good.
I have done many survival shows so far,
but surviving like this feels so good.
The chef from Min's.
He worked really hard by my side,
plating the food and even serving it himself.
Even when his own orders were coming in,
he was busy helping me.
I felt so sorry, yet truly grateful.
When the name Lee Yeon Bok was called, I felt so great.
I felt like I was Chef Wang.
(Standing ovation)
I'm so happy for you.
You warmed up after a long time.
- I know.
- It's been a while.
The assistant was good, right?
I should treat him to a good meal.
You did so well.
- You were super fast.
- I was fast.
In a way, Ho Yoon should have finished way earlier.
I know.
There's an emotion here that I have never felt before in my entire life.
(Kim Ho Yoon, Orders: 30, Served: 26)
When the finish line is just around the corner,
you want to go fast, and you feel a surge of energy.
But if you fail to pace yourself at that moment,
the chances of stumbling right before the finish line seem to rise.
(Kim Ho Yoon wipes every bowl until the very end.)
Let's go.
Just send them out quickly.
Sending them out is what is important.
He does his best until the very end.
Yes, that is what being a pro is.
This is the top blade steak pasta.
- He focuses on details.
- You can combine them freely...
when you eat picnic meal.
Please take your order.
It's top blade steak pasta.
(Kim Ho Yoon completed selling 30 orders.)
Good job.
- Done.
- It's over.
We have the second survivor.
The second survivor is...
Kim Ho Yoon.
Please move to the Survival Room immediately.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
I wish you good luck.
(The second survivor of the boss battle: Kim Ho Yoon)
(He survived only in 53 minutes.)
Please move to the Survival Room immediately.
This really...
makes your blood run dry.
I can't believe I went through an experience like this twice.
You returned alive from the inferno.
I know.
(Kim Ho Yoon returned alive from the inferno once again.)
I was so happy.
I wanted to give him a hug.
Ho Yoon, you're so tenacious.
You revived twice.
He really is. Twice.
(The 2 with the 7-sectioned plate took 1st and 2nd places.)
Edward Kwon.
Four orders remain until reaching thirty orders.
- You have four orders left.
- Four orders remaining.
Four orders remain.
- He has four orders left.
- My goodness.
Completion is what matters.
What is going on? It is non-stop plot twists.
(At that moment, Lee Sung Hoon)
We need to send this out fast.
(Edward Kwon: 4 orders needed)
(Lee Sung Hoon: 4 orders to serve)
(Lee Sung Hoon received 30 orders 1st,)
(but he takes long to send the dishes out.)
(On the other hand, Edward Kwon serves food immediately upon order.)
Please enjoy your meal. Here's your pasta.
(He will be eliminated if he fails...)
(to serve 7 orders before Edward Kwon.)
(Go Seok Hyun was serving two menu items simultaneously.)
(Big cream shrimps and futomaki, special mixed tendon)
Wait. We need to send them out quickly so you can win.
No, let's do it together.
You only have seven orders to serve.
Perfect.
Nice.
I didn't know I was a kingmaker. Let's go.
- Give me the fried food.
- Okay.
I wanted at least one of us to survive.
I decided to bet on where the chances were higher.
- We'll keep going like this.
- Okay.
I thought it would be better to support him.
Let's go.
No making the same mistake twice. Let's go.
You have only seven dishes to go.
(The last 7 tendon bowls are filling up quickly.)
I'm short one shrimp.
- I will give you mine.
- Thank you.
It was a truly touching moment.
There was only one survival spot left,
and he just told me to use his ingredient.
He told me to just send the tendon out quickly...
and that he would help me.
I'll make sure to repay your kindness.
What are you talking about? Just keep working.
It's hot.
(Filling up the 7 tendon bowls)
Send the tendon out quickly.
- Three are going out now.
- Okay.
Here's your food. Enjoy it.
- Thank you.
(Lee Sung Hoon, Orders: 32, Served: 28)
Let's finish this in one shot.
(Edward Kwon is also clearing his orders rapidly.)
(Currently 27 out of 30 orders)
Here's your pasta.
Edward Kwon.
A plate is added to Edward Kwon as a penalty.
(Currently 27 out of 31 orders)
Oh, no!
This is the most delicious thing I have ever eaten.
- Right?
- I find it a little too salty.
- What? Really?
- The pasta is a little too salty.
I started nagging myself...
little by little again.
(He constantly reheated...)
(and checked the food worrying it might get cold.)
The penalty honestly hurts my pride so much.
Seriously.
I think Young Min is almost done.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I know.
They cannot make mistakes now.
- Here's your pasta.
- Thank you.
Yes. Have a nice day.
If I didn't receive the penalty, I'd be done after just one dish.
(Ordering)
(Currently 29 out of 31 orders)
(An added order)
Edward Kwon...
has received 30 orders.
Let's go, Young Min!
- We don't know it yet.
- How will it go?
So the tendon can't keep up with that.
- What?
- They just need to serve it.
- Currently, the team leaders...
- Please.
who got orders over 30 servings are...
Edward Kwon and Lee Sung Hoon.
Tendon is ready.
Only 1 will survive between the 2.
Here's your pasta. Enjoy.
(Meanwhile, Edward Kwon serves his 30th order.)
One more to go. Let's go.
Focus. I can do it.
Anyone who got a call for tendon?
(A customer is standing in front of Aunties Kitchen.)
Yes, there are.
Do you want to get this?
You got it. Hurry up and serve.
(The order is in.)
Isn't Young Min done?
- Edward Kwon is done.
- He's done.
- Tendon is done.
- Tendon is done too.
But they were very close.
- Go.
- Did you get a call?
This is so dramatic.
- We have...
- Edward.
the last survivor.
The last survivor is...
Here comes the delicious pasta.
- Yes, just one. Done.
- Done.
The last survivor is...
Lee Sung Hoon.
Please move to the Survival Room immediately.
- What?
Lee Sung Hoon.
Who is it?
The difference between him and Edward Kwon was...
just one.
(Just one)
Gosh.
My goodness.
That's crazy.
Well done, Young Min.
I think I'm going to cry.
- My goodness.
- This is unpredictable.
He must be so sad.
Just one order away?
Congratulations.
Can you believe it? Just one?
Thank you.
Congratulations.
I was happy...
to survive. But at the same time,
I felt bad...
for Team Agungi.
Happiness 51 and sorrow 49.
But then I'm really happy for him.
I wish he wins in the final round.
I'm sorry, and thank you.
Congratulations. That's great.
I'm happy, yet...
(The final survivor is Lee Sung Hoon.)
I don't know what to do.
(Go Seok Hyun's number of orders: 29)
I deep-fried all the shrimp.
- Okay.
- I think it's enough for ten bowls.
- Over ten.
- That's perfect.
Futomaki is ready.
Thank you. Enjoy.
(Sniffing)
Will you make the futomaki?
Two futomakis.
- Two?
- Yes.
That was really close.
(Sniffing)
Futomaki is ready.
Futomaki.
Take the drink with you.
Thank you.
(The business of boss battle ends.)
I think Edward is one order short.
(When he was going neck-and-neck with Lee Sung Hoon a minute ago...)
You got it. Hurry up and serve.
(The customer who was standing in front of Aunties Kitchen...)
(Kim Mi Ryeong, Edward Kwon)
Do you want to get this?
(Kim Mi Ryeong)
- It's here.
- What is it?
It's for you.
(Kim Mi Ryeong got the last order.)
I was one order short.
Darn it.
The last survivor is...
- You're one short?
- Lee Sung Hoon.
- Darn it.
- Please move...
- I just have one order left.
- to the Survival Room immediately.
What can I do?
- That's so close.
- What can I do?
I just have one left.
It made me upset.
I expected it to be Edward Kwon.
- Me too.
- I thought he won.
He's making history today.
Well done.
- Good job.
- Well done, buddy.
It was so close. I watched everything.
- Well done, chef.
- Good job.
He did a good job like a pro.
Business is never predictable until you try it.
It's never predictable.
I have to face it.
What can I do?
There's nothing I can do about it.
We need to eat something.
This goes well with tangsuyuk.
It's very fresh.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
The five restaurants that failed to survive...
are officially closing.
Good job. You did well.
No.
Five restaurants that failed to survive...
must...
close the restaurants immediately.
(Agungi)
I hate to close it.
During this survival,
I learned...
what usually took me 2 or 3 years to learn...
at every mission.
I learned a lot.
I felt the wall big time.
I felt many walls, but I'll continue to try...
and create that wall myself one day.
I'll try again.
(Min's)
Honestly, it's bittersweet.
Come and try it.
I was happy. I had fun.
But at the same time, it was annoying and stressful.
I thought I could reach higher.
I'll take this as a sign to work harder...
and I'll do my best.
Good job.
You worked hard for two months.
(Gotgan)
I guess I'm still not good at business.
Give it to me.
I grew attached to the restaurant.
It broke my heart to put an X on it.
(Mom and son)
Only if I'd done a little better.
It's already fun to work with my son.
I wanted to give him good experience.
My son is who I trust the most.
As someone I work with in the kitchen,
I want to give him a credit for that.
I want to tell him that he did a good job.
I think I'm going to cry.
That's what I want to say.
(Ma Restaurant)
I think I learned so much.
I enjoyed each day.
Even though we're friends,
we never talked so much on the phone before.
I think we made an average of five calls a day.
I'm serious.
It was nice to meet all these nice people.
Above all, I was able to make good memories with my friend.
I think I'll never forget that for the rest of my life.
This business survival show...
will become...
an unforgettable memory in my life.
I'm thankful to him.
What are you doing? Are you crying?
Come on.
Why are you crying?
Don't cry.
It's not easy to see a Busan man cry.
- Good job, buddy.
- Well done.
You were great.
I'll make it cool.
This is the second time we're drawing it.
(Everything About Tteokbokki)
I already knew...
that we didn't have enough.
(Near the end of the match)
- Producer.
- Yes?
I can't sell anymore. I ran out of tteokbokki.
We didn't have enough rice cake to start with.
No rice cake.
This is all we have. We gave out too much earlier.
I thought we still had a lot left.
I used it all.
(Kwan Hoon used too much rice cake.)
Do you have rice? Either cooked or uncooked.
- No.
- No?
Do you have rice? Either cooked or uncooked.
We don't have any rice.
In the comeback round,
I made rice cake with rice.
To do that again,
I asked around for rice.
But I couldn't find any rice.
I did my best to find a replacement...
for rice cake...
and made it with a lot of ingredients other than rice cake.
I ran out of ingredients. I can't sell any more.
It won't be enough.
(Giving up with 6 orders left)
Honestly, I thought about...
serving all ten...
by giving less.
But I couldn't do it.
What's the point...
of lying to people just to win?
This is a bummer.
(A generous amount to the end)
I'm giving a lot for the last one.
Kim Kwan Hoon gives up due to shortage of ingredients.
The last one.
Of course, it was such a bummer.
But under the name of Everything About Tteokbokki,
with tteokbokki and fritters,
we've had a lot of...
fun and exciting experience.
I owe it to you.
It was an honor. Thank you.
The five closed restaurants...
must leave the Street Arena...
immediately.
(Leave the Street Arena.)
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Good job.
- Well done.
- Good work.
Bye. Good luck.
Good luck.
- Hey.
- You must win.
- Good luck.
- I'm rooting for you.
- See you.
- Good job.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
It was so much fun.
Yes, it was really fun.
Well done.
Good job. You worked hard.
(Ma Restaurant)
I can keep going.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
The seven restaurants that survived...
the 100 serving relay team match. Congratulations.
- Good job.
We will now reveal the total revenue...
- for Round Three.
- Right.
I totally forgot...
- about the revenue.
- Me too.
The total revenue you made today...
is 9,689 dollars.
After adding all revenues from all rounds,
the total amount of the prize money...
is 172,872.16 dollars.
- It's 170,000 dollars.
- It's 170,000 dollars?
I'm starting to see the prize money.
The only restaurant...
that survives to the end...
will have the prize money.
That's almost 200,000 dollars.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
We will now reveal the mission and the commercial area for Round Four.
- What?
- Now?
They'll tell us now?
- They'll tell us now?
- Now?
The commercial area and the mission.
For the mission and the commercial area for Round Four,
(Looking around)
you'll move there and check.
- What?
- Where? We're going there?
- Where are we going?
- We don't know.
- Where is it?
- Where could it be?
- Are we going somewhere like this?
- What?
We're rivals now.
We're rivals.
Friends today, enemies tomorrow.
Where are they taking us?
Where are we going?
We're leaving right away.
- This is tense.
- So tense.
I wonder where they're taking us.
The windows are covered.
Oh, you're right.
They're blocking the front.
- The front too?
- They're closing the curtains.
- So we can't see the front.
- The front too?
The back too. What's happening?
(The sight is completely covered.)
I was very nervous.
"Where on earth are we going?"
"Are we going to start as soon as we get off?"
It's probably not somewhere ordinary.
I'm getting scared.
(Moving to the unknown place for the mission)
- They're not saying we arrived.
- I know.
It feels like we're going in circles.
How can it keep going without stopping?
It barely stopped.
We didn't stop at the traffic light, right?
Exactly.
I can never guess.
It seems the city lights are gone.
That's what I mean.
What's happening?
I can't wait to find out where we're going.
(While they're making guesses on the mission area,)
(the bus stops.)
We're here.
- Really?
- We're here.
I see a dim light, but I can't tell where we are.
What?
This is crazy.
- Where are we?
- We're at the airport.
Really?
This is crazy.
I think we're going abroad.
Which airport? Incheon or...
- We're in Incheon.
- Incheon?
(Incheon International Airport)
We're at Incheon Airport.
What are we doing at the airport?
This is crazy.
What are we doing here?
Why are we at Incheon Airport at this hour?
- I could never imagine.
- Me neither.
I never expected to go to the airport.
Where are we going?
(They don't know where the mission will be taking place yet.)
We're going inside?
This way?
I never thought I'd get to enter here.
What on earth...
are we doing here?
I have no clue.
Are they taking us abroad?
What can we do here?
(War)
This is war.
Of course, this is war.
There's war going on. It's a complete mess.
There's no war like that.
(War)
(Airport War)
(The semifinal will determine Top 7's destiny.)
(An average of 200,000 visitors a day)
(Round 4, Breakfast at Airport)
(The food court in the departure area)
(7 brands will open at the airport.)
(For the customers who are departing,)
(compete with breakfast.)
(We have to stay up all night.)
(The bidding war for the restaurant and the promotional items)
(- It's all about the location. - I must secure it.)
(Let's mess it up.)
(Bring it on.)
(Think fast...)
(to get what you want.)
(Sold for...)
(That place is...)
(complete war.)
(These pricks are taking them already.)
(The big pot... They took it already.)
(Kitchen war)
(I could become a marathoner after this.)
(The real game begins now.)
(Amidst pouring orders...)
(This could be the edge of the cliff.)
(The match that tests the limit of your strength)
(It's really good, though.)
(That's the airport food.)
(Who will get chosen by the travelers...)
(and win the ticket to the final?)